We'll call the Board of the Mimes,
especially until they've known the Board of Directors
for a second.
We'll call the Board of Directors for the Education
by Patrick Grace Church.
Bill Charts.
Pleasure to honor the year tonight to offer
our prayer on behalf of our community and our leaders.
I appreciate the opportunity to begin
asking the value and so it's been more of a prayer.
I'd probably thank you tonight for this wonderful town
that we have been able to live here
for decades, on decades, seven new times.
But Lord, we ask God to give this council
of this, the leaders, the mayor, the city, the manager,
the attorney, all the city heads,
wisdom, grace, and strength to the better
in the work community.
We just ask God to just have a divine
protection over those that serve us, like in the fire department,
the civil servants, the police department.
And we ask God to just help us to grow our city
as the church community comes together,
pray and set you a healer land.
And we set it for tonight, or we turn to you.
And we ask God to bless our city,
bless our workers, bless our leaders, and Jesus.
Amen.
Congratulations.
Good to have you to apply to the United States of America.
And we should be doing a lot of, we're just saying,
I'm a nation, I don't know you got it.
In New Israel, we've never seen you just as our all.
Good.
Thank you, Lord, good.
Thank you, Lord.
Good.
Thank you.
Okay.
All right.
We will slide the talker.
Okay.
Thank you for the support of the audience.
Sorry.
So, Mr. Mayor, this was the new place in the last week.
We will be able to know how I made it because it was reached out to you to another.
That we were able to circle up and utilize the importance of the place that we are out.
You and I can summarize this.
You and I have met in the two of those places with a title of mine, mine by the line,
because we have written this question and reached a consensus.
Okay.
Will you prove it and present it back to the council?
We shall be ready.
Please, you're right.
It would be best to be no proof what the truth is in that case.
So, do you go home?
Five.
Lewis.
Four.
Five.
pressure and some of the other inductions out there. So, OGA is asked as they will not
allow us to put a tower on them. I'm basically going to lay in there so they are
selling at those apart from the land so we can put our tower on there because they
have no equal anymore. So, this is just a part of just those apart from the land and this will
just come out of our operating budget that we have for the city. So, where is these tower?
Um, they have anything to look on the packet to show, hey, just here.
It's at 69 a.m. off bail. So right there, there's a little triangle in the overpass.
Would be where the top of the triangle will be as wider.
A lot of them will run off on that curve right there. They need to do something.
Oh, I'm a way might not.
So, we have part of our human way to go on and for water improvements and one of the
water paying so there's really just item the water to hang out with.
Do you have questions about the number?
Most of it, would we move?
Well, we have three times of the four-day.
Number five.
Theruptus.
Theralal data.
The Mal軍 recruitment.
The number of best ill miser alleg 느낄
is zero.
Eight twenty-one out what stretches of 20
linear width of 15 HDBC and sub.
And so there's a encoding on that kind of a part
of a familiar frequency with a decaying height
in the genetic and satellite message.
So when we add the conversion of the watt via
So that's what we're going to do.
So we're out there to be for the opposite of the Janet expand and also to be ready for any other expansion that's on
But we're allowed to know also the permit number W
Zero zero zero by eight to zero. They take two construction of about four and eight five
Your feet native
So this is for if you notice I'm off of
I'm streaked the theory of tribe of doing their development back there with the buildings
So the tribe has got an armament and they will put the water on and they will give it back to the city to maintain that
That's our map to be the city's name. So this is the acknowledging that permit the first one is for water and it's like one is for the serial
So, is there
For the 13 sector project staff recommendation that will work bit the sea 20 that should be six for substations skated
A gradation black rock automation
Even
Came back
And that's been the member to symbolize here where your record is.
So we only have one bear with the SEL
Came in quail budget
So we rejected rebate
It's got three bitters this time
And black rock automation came in
Well under budget
So called talk to them
They're comfortable with the scope. They're comfortable with their price
They're in the current hope it
How much out of weather weather
No, we were budgeting
Two and a half or three hundred is what you were budgeting
So I mean there are a hundred thousand dollars under
I mean I'm not going to say that not slide in there
Because it is
So I was going to ask
I'm not going to ask
We call black rock
And check with them because any time you have this word that is correctly seen you want to make sure they didn't forget something
And normally out of this faith we've given the option to step away
Without keeping it with bonds
And they were comfortable with everything
Stand behind their cost, they stand behind the scope of the work that's required
They are a lot smaller functioning of the SEL
And also for the others
And you work with them a lot
I haven't
They've done a bunch of work in the oil and gas industry in Texas
And we've checked in with some of those guys that have been happy with them
I don't know if I'm going to visit you
I do not know off top of my head.
I do know what you're at.
So tell you, so you're selected in our list.
Yes.
So what out here is if we accept this tonight,
we would set down with a city,
old city, old city,
and go do line line.
If you already have one,
but just to me,
all of us will know for like,
you're sure you know,
there's the other one.
Yes.
So are you asking,
we approve this?
Yes.
I'm going to do that.
So we can get to that point.
Because I know they're wanting to know what we do.
And the other thing is,
I mean, I've also talked about there's a lot of money in it,
probably for engineering.
So they're engineering,
being able to achieve it,
and as the oldest,
I can better.
And this is just viewboard.
We still have to go through the entire
contract process.
We get them hired.
And so that's all contingent on us
to do everything.
We need to actually sign contracts.
So you need to get out of the building.
Exactly.
If any point through this whole process,
something is pummeling or we're not feeling good about it.
We can stop and we'll come back and talk to you again.
And we'll move on to the next one.
I'd like to go through.
Second.
The grant was, I think, at that time,
it was around 13,000, the ability,
which was, was there a match on our internet,
just fully, that was for the whole deal.
So I think it was like, 25, 75,
great at that time.
And I was, my first step would be to reach out
to go it off to see if I could find anything,
because it was from 2019, 2010.
So there's, obviously, in the picture,
there's in the center of the road between maintenance and control.
I think, you know, I really don't want to put it in the center of the road.
But there was, if you look there,
two right in front of the security bank,
there wasn't concrete.
I'm happy that the design and order port is set on.
So one of those things is somehow about the project kind of go.
It's a security bank.
I'm still looking at the beginning.
All that right up to you is more someone is saying,
sir, I want to make other counsel.
We'll be with it before we start going down the path.
So, in the afternoon, I have an answer to that.
I don't know.
I mean, I don't know.
And I don't know.
So the primary objective here that we'll be to go out and look
and see if those are answerable.
First of all.
Yes.
This is what we do a lot of.
Because when we don't want to see what's wrong,
we have to sit down with him.
And they said, we never thought, why don't we go to the afternoon.
Or if he had to go to the court today.
So, he would mean to say, if it does come up,
if he would be ordered.
If he had to say, if he would come up to the court,
he would come up to the court.
Yeah.
Or I mean, we would, you know, we'd been in
it out just to see what the price would actually be.
Or the price would actually be for the blind.
And we'd bring that back to the afternoon.
Because it is such a different.
I don't know.
I can go to the card for us as to make what the call
to do that.
And that's a pretty different call for him.
And if anyone has an actual call,
I'm sure of it.
It would be awesome.
Because I can find a blind and blind.
So.
Yeah.
Or the other side.
Because personally, I want to know, like, you know,
what if you're going down to the digital piece of the show.
Because the show is having off to the river.
I mean, you can't even know where to go.
What year was this?
Thank you.
You know.
And you know, okay.
So you'd be a big deal to hold that.
You're nothing.
Yeah.
I was like the biggest beauty of the show.
I was like, like, I don't know.
Do they conquer or never be?
No.
Good.
I don't know.
No.
Can I imagine the 1960s, if you would be blind,
Give me a big blind idea.
Like.
That.
Second.
I'm a lot of customers who've been saying about things that have come up recently, but
continue to build a writing on time, about some who say that you're not even going to
build on.
actually a few days, just on the way to the point where you know it's supposed to pay.
I've seen somewhere through a state that they're dropping in a drop box and it's not supposed to be called days.
Just one of the different things like that, there's discussions of where there's no educational shut-offs.
I saw all the policies recently on the flight yesterday that there's an option to be called,
to me to call, of course, in defense, in a system of hunger, in my own model.
Despite areas that we do, some things may be different to be more beneficial to more customers.
Like, as far as bills arriving late, or payments, we're going through the mineral arriving late,
the ADD and the TNH degrees, so they've got all of them.
As far as maybe, as far as the customers being aware of the shut-off,
maybe when they call in, they ask the question, you know,
if I ever change a phone number, if only my first explanation of all the city of what you know,
I have a phone number.
And just kind of want to know if those cities in our system would try to make this thing more beneficial for the customers.
Also, previously, it was stated that the city would get to arrest the banks that didn't have
an agreement for payments to be made there.
And there's a few banks and a lot to do that before you experience where we're out with that.
And then some of the complaints are basically saying the options when they come in are basically paid a day
or be shut off.
A little confused by that.
According to what I read on the policy, it states that the shut-off's going to be the day
of a last day of the 10th day after the day.
The shut-off's will be the 11th day.
But the thing is, what it seems a little bit certain is, some customers are not even in a bank of their
payment and they're saying that they're not offered one or maybe they could go on that empty plan.
They're probably not either.
So basically, it's like, are we doing anything to have to offer them an option,
or just saying, you know, if you don't pay this, it's a shut-off.
One of the comments that I saw is that the guys are going to be shut off over 12 o'clock
and I would just want to make sure that, you know, we're all options worse,
or prior to showing something off over 12,000.
I've seen people say I've lived at 30-40 years, never been living by life.
I don't get it for the new day, and it's late because it's going to shut down.
I don't put that on the patient itself.
Just want to see if there's some things we can do if it's just a play.
Mayor, we're responding.
So Mr. Floating and I have had many, many conversations to brought a lot of these
to my attention, and I've had some opportunities to not only address some of these,
but kind of dive into them with staff and kind of,
it's really going to good opportunity for me as well to kind of learn a lot of the policy
and rules that we have in life, right?
So...
And as Josh has brought them up, and we looked at them, and we were going to be there.
There's opportunities for us to review our policies and find out, you know, have things changed,
has the environment changed, which has the technology changed.
You know, in this particular situation, we've just got some great examples of, you know,
our use of the post office and the challenges that we have there, how can we address that.
One of the things I would like to do, because I do have some good information that Josh and I need to
to probably go over the technical activity.
Mr. Planning is all made in a number of order of mayor's citizens.
He is, maybe with Mr. Planning's help, we present these to that committee.
Not only discuss and explain some of the information that I was able to gather,
but further down that dialogue, where the technical author has been made come up with some
opportunities, and then come back and there's that many opportunities that we find
to move into the council and have possible changes in the implementation of the challenge.
I mean, I understand that the post-laced and in part of the next phase might not be the solution,
maybe there's something in the community or maybe it would be better to change what some challenges
like the solution would better to be re-growing and letting the action be better in the
discussion on what the post-laced and what the people want.
I think they would be very delighted to have a session.
Thank you, Josh.
Thank you.
16, staff of course.
17, trustee.
Thank you.